["Love In Suburbia"
by Danny Connors playing]
♪ Woo-hoo, woo-hoo, woo-hoo... ♪
[woman] Ben and I have been friends
for a year and a half.
He's brilliantly smart.
He's compassionate.
He is a diamond in the rough,
and I don't think women appreciate it.
♪ All I wanna do... ♪
[man]
Ben is looking for the love of his life.
When women say that they want to meet
a funny, emotional, caring man...
Ben is that person.
♪ Is fall in love
In suburbia with you... ♪
[man] I've known been since he's moved
to New Orleans two years ago.
He's a hopeless romantic
who has a great heart and great charisma.
In the modern dating scene,
those things are overlooked.
[woman] Ben is too good for this world.
He is the most dateable guy I know.
-But truly, truly nice guys finish last.
-[exhales]
-Hello.
-Hi.
-[Jaden] Hey.
-[chuckles]
-It's nice to meet you.
[both laughing]
I... I'm, uh...[stutters]
[laughing] Why not both?
-Okay, what's your name?
-I'm Ben.
-Ben. I'm Jaden. It's nice to meet you.
-And it's nice to meet you.
-I, uh...
-These are for me?
-They are for you.
-Okay.
I don't think
I've ever gotten flowers before.
-Well, hopefully, it's good. [chuckles]
-Yeah, it's a very good thing. Thank you.
I'm not 100% sure
what kind of flowers those are.
I think they might be chrysanthemums.
So you brought me something
you don't know--
No, I'm just joking. [laughs]
Only the finest.
-Have you ever been here?
-I haven't.
I haven't either. [chuckles]
-It's gonna be a great experience.
-It's gonna-- We don't know the flowers.
We don't know the restaurant.
We don't know each other.
-I'm excited.
-[laughs] Riddles are great. We'll learn.
-We'll learn all of these things.
-Yes.
-You ready?
-Want to go in?
-Yeah, let's do it.
-Great.
-After you.
-Thank you.
[Ben] Do you want to get a drink
at the bar?
Sure.
-Can I--Can I get your chair for you?
-Thank you.
-You're a gentleman.
-Oh, yeah. Well, what can I say? It was...
mostly ready already.
[both laughing]
What can I get for y'all?
Uh, may I please grab a Tito's and soda
with a splash of cranberry and lime?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
Um, I think I'll just have
a Dark 'n' Stormy.
A Dark 'n Stormy. Fantastic.
-Have that out in just a minute.
-Thank you so much.
Easy order.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I-- I'm... [stammers]
Prior to coming to New Orleans,
I was never much of a drinker.
And I'm still kind of not much
of a drinker, if I'm being honest,
but this city has its way...
-of kind of pulling that out of you.
-Definitely does.
I'm a huge closet nerd.
-I love Dragon Ball Z.
-Okay, yeah.
So, so, so, I... I...
[stammers] I confess that is
an acquired taste that I never acquired.
I understand completely.
Have you watched, um...
Avatar: The Last Airbender?
I feel like I watched it
a bazillion years ago
-and don't remember anything about it.
-Oh, Jaden, oh.
I'll have to watch it.
It is one of the greatest television shows
ever created.
All right, tell me about yourself.
What do you do?
Okay. Uh, I am a professor...
-Really?
-...of computer science.
-Up at the University of New Orleans.
-Amazing.
Thank you.
Yeah. So I'm a full-time student.
-Mechanical engineering.
-Exciting!
Oh, that's awesome.
Where do you go to school?
Uh, to University of New Orleans.
Which is nearby.
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah. Okay, great.
I'm... Uh, uh... I'm so sorry
for getting a weird look on my face.
I... [stammers] I am a professor
at the University of New Orleans.
-Oh, are you?
-Yeah.
Nice. [chuckles]
Yeah.
So I...
I am not sure if we are allowed...
-to be here with each other right now.
-[chuckling]
But you're not...
my student.
-You are not my professor.
-Yeah.
I have no power over what grades you have.
-Yes.
-I don't know any of your professors.
-I think that we should be okay.
-I think we should be okay.
-[Shamerick] This is exciting.
-[Ben] Yeah.
Cheers.
-[chuckles] Cheers.
-Cheers to a good night.
-To a good night.
-Yes.
-Have you ever been here before?
-Uh, uh, uh, just once or twice.
I've played a little jazz trio gig.
-No way!
-Yeah.
-That's amazing.
[stammers] Uh, I... What...
Did you... did you sing?
Did you play an instrument?
Yeah, I sang and played guitar,
and had an upright bass player
and saxophone, so...
That's incredible. I, uh...
I certainly don't want
to misrepresent myself,
but, uh, in my youth, like growing up,
I took a lot of singing classes and--
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Did you do musicals?
-I did.
-You did musicals?
-I did, yes!
-Yes, I did.
-My gosh, me too.
-Oh, my gosh.
-We should go audition together.
-I would totally--
-Would you?
-Yeah.
-I think...
-Are you just saying--
No, I am not saying that.
So I think there's, um, a production
coming up of Oliver!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
So I was a dancer. I danced in college.
-More for fun.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I was a writer for a magazine here.
-No way.
I have modeled here for many years.
Well, that makes sense.
Then I got into real estate
and I love the autonomy and...
What... [stammers]
-The autonomy.
-Autonomy, sorry.
Sorry. No, yeah, yeah, um, uh...
The accent.
Oh, no, no. [laughing]
-Is that a Mississippi twang? [chuckles]
-Southern thing, yes.
And I'm-- I'm a California boy.
Really?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I am not from California.
-Okay. Okay.
-I'm from Prairieville.
-I don't know what that is.
-Uh, it is exactly how it sounds.
It is Hicksville, USA.
Um, so I was born in Lafayette.
So you're... you're from New Orleans.
-I would say so, yeah.
-Yeah.
Yeah, born and raised.
-[Ben] No way?
-Yeah.
I actually have, uh, two homes, so I--
-You have two homes?
-Well, my... [laughing]
-That's...
-Yeah. So I go back and forth...
um, because, um, I have children.
[gasps]
-Yeah.
-Cool.
-I have two boys.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Awesome.
Uh, um...
-Do you have any children?
-I do not. No.
Do you want kids?
-[stuttering]
-[chuckling]
With your career path, is that in it?
So-- Man. Okay.
Um, I...
[stammers]
Like, the short answer is "yes."
[waiter]
Hey, guys. I've got your table ready.
-Right over here.
-Perfect. Great.
Uh, I guess...
[chuckles] So sorry.
It's a delicate operation.
Can I get your drink for you?
-Please.
-Yeah.
-[waiter] Right over here.
-Great.
-[scoffs] I'm starving.
-Me too.
-Oh, Perfect timing.
-[waiter] Hey, guys. Welcome.
-Hi.
Thank you. [chuckles]
Thank you so much. It's beautiful.
[laughing]
[singing indistinctly, inhales]
Uh...
-You're funny.
Okay. [laughing]
Oh, would you not like to be funny?
-No, that's cool. I can be funny.
-Ah. Great.
I'm definitely going with the gnocchi.
Yes, I am too.
I love the gnocchi.
-That's what I want too.
-Okay, perfect! Great.
It's one thing we have in common,
for sure.
Good. Yeah. [laughs] Thank goodness.
I was just kidding.
[Ben] Um...
So, I...
I'm curious. Like...
-Okay. About?
-Like...
Do you go on dates often?
I do. Uh, well, actually, not recently.
I kind of took a break
from the dating scene,
-because it's, uh, exhausting.
-Yeah! [laughing]
-[Alex] I work a lot.
-Yes.
So it doesn't leave a lot of time
for dating or meeting people.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's been interesting having...
having been engaged for, like,
two or more years.
Yeah, it's scary.
-Especially at this age.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Going back into--
-Getting back out there.
Most people are married with children.
On their second marriage.
Uh-huh! And there's that sense of like,
"Oh, my gosh,
I have these things that I--"
Clock is ticking.
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
-It's daunting.
It's terrifying.
So what about you?
Tell me something about...
Tell me-- Tell you something about me?
Tell me something about yourself
that I don't know.
-Which could be anything.
-Okay, anything. Whoo, whoo, uh...
-[chuckles]
-Well, I have...
uh, basically not dated at all
in some ways.
-I...
-Okay.
I've had, uh...
Uh... one of the first...
and only women that I ever dated...
Uh, we were dating
for about ten and a half years.
-[Kat] Okay.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah...
-Feel ya.
Yeah. Yeah?
-Eight and a half.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-Ended in March.
Okay. So you're still
kind of fresh off of that?
I mean-- I didn't--
Like, everyone's process is different.
[Shamerick] It's time to live.
It is time to live.
We've been in these relationships
for a long time.
-Yeah.
-And now I feel like...
I don't know. Benjamin Button, but, like,
backwards, reversed. You know what I mean?
Wait, wait. Benjamin Button reversed
is just normal. [laughs]
Okay, right. Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry.
-Look, forget that part.
-[laughs]
The food's here.
Okay. Perfect. Perfect timing.
-This looks delicious.
-Thank you so much.
I'm slow. Don't wait for me.
Feel free to dig in.
[chuckles]
[giggles]
Thank you.
-I love gnocchi.
-Yeah, yeah.
Hard to go wrong.
Um, I...
So, this is the first blind date
-that you've ever been on?
-Oh, yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
-A hundred percent.
-I think it's going very well.
-I know. I like it.
-Blind dates...
-Not too bad.
-Not too shabby.
Um, so you have...
a family.
You've got a couple of kids.
Are you interested
in having any more kids?
I am actually.
It shocks people, 'cause I'm like,
"Look, I'm open to whatever."
-You never know what the future...
-Yeah.
...is gonna hold.
I'm either going to never have kids
or I'm going to adopt.
-Interesting. Yeah.
-Yeah.
Growing up in Prairieville, Louisiana,
you go on a date with a guy
and you tell him you don't want kids?
Oh, my God.
Smoke trail.
Oh... [stuttering] the Road Runner?
"You don't want my spawn?"
'Cause God forbid,
everybody in Prairieville thinks
they have, you know, the golden seed.
[laughs] I'm sorry.
That's wildly inappropriate. [chuckles]
Um... [chuckles, inhales] Uh...
No comment.
No comment on my seed.
[laughing]
Um...
[Stephanie] New Orleans is beautiful.
And I'm-- And I'm so proud to be--
To call this place home. I really am.
What... What was it like
living through Katrina?
Um, I was still fairly young
when it happened.
I can't say, like,
I have too many memories.
Maybe, for some reason,
you just block some memories out.
Yeah. It's...
amazing, the scar it's left on the city.
Definitely.
[stammers] But also,
any other city in the world,
if that happened to it,
it would just be gone.
But there's something about...
this city that just inspires people
to, like, cling on.
A city is just a bunch of buildings,
right?
But, like, until you fill it with people.
And I guess-- I just-- Again, I'm...
Wow, yeah. It's weird that I'm getting
emotional. I'm getting worked up about it.
I think that the people of New Orleans
are absolutely incredible.
Well, we're glad to have you. [laughs]
Thank you. [laughs]
Um, uh, I would love to know
just, like, what you like to do for fun?
Actually, I just recently started
-hosting a radio show.
-No way?
It's like a musicians and artists
mental wellness type show.
But music that we find healing.
That is incredible. I...
I asked you what you do for fun
and what you do for fun is help other
people be the best that they can be.
-Didn't think about it like that.
-That's amazing.
Uh...
I'm having a really...
-awesome time with you.
-I am too.
Do you maybe want to, like...
-Go to another place?
-...go to a--
-Get some drinks or something?
-Sure.
Wait, I can't leave my flowers.
I'm touched. [laughs]
You thought I would forget? Oh, no.
-[Kat] Shall we?
-I think we shall. [laughing]
So, do you have any favorite places
in New Orleans that you go to?
-Uh, uh, yeah.
-Like what?
Actually, have you ever been to...
Uh... Ooh, ooh...
Lebanon Cafe? Cafe Lebanon?
No, but that's one of my favorite
types of food, so...
-Great.
-Gonna have to keep that in mind.
Yeah. Well, maybe...
-[mumbling]
-[chuckling]
Um... So...
I had...
a really incredible time.
Uh, but I... I also...
[stammers] I, uh...
Even though it's probably totally fine
and there's nothing to worry about,
I'm a professor, you're a student,
we're at the same university.
Before...
we see each other again, if you even
wanted to see each other again...
I would feel more comfortable
just checking in with human resources
at UNO.
I just-- I think everyone involved
would feel more comfortable.
-Definitely.
-I just...
Um...
Yeah. Uh...
So I...
might call you a Lyft right now?
-Yeah.
-Great.
Um...
[mumbling] Um...
I do the usual stuff.
-I like to read, I like to watch TV.
-[laughing]
I like to play video games.
-I'm a video game professor.
-Me too.
-Really?
-Yes.
-What's your favorite game?
-FIFA.
Amazing!
Is that yours?
I'm not so into sports games, but I--
-Do you like Dance Dance Revolution?
-[laughing]
-I love Dance Dance Revolution.
-So you think you can dance?
[laughs]
-Do you think you can tap dance?
-Well...
Well, my mom might have something
to say about that.
Let's... Shall we?
Oh!
Is that a challenge? A tap-off?
[stammers] Are you challenging me to a--
Oh, God. You've already won.
[laughing]
Can you wing?
-Uh, is that...
-Yes!
Flap, flap, flap.
-So impressed.
-[laughs]
Your mom would be proud actually.
That was...
-that was beautiful.
-Impressed.
-You really can dance.
-[laughs]
Well, thank you so much for tonight.
It's been great.
I had such a great time meeting you.
It's been so wonderful
meeting you, Stephanie.
-I hope we get to see each other again.
-I hope so too.
Yeah.
Let me get the door for you.
Uh...
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Take care, Stephanie.
-Thank you.
[Stephanie] Good night.
Good night.
This is actually
the place I was thinking of.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Want to try it out?
-If it looks okay...
Yeah, we should...
We should probably--
It's a little rude
to go into another establishment with--
We'd better-- We don't want to be...
-Ugly.
-Mm-mm.
-All right, let's do it. Let's go in.
-Okay, let's go. Let's do it.
-[chuckling]
-Time once more into the breach.
Here?
Thank you.
-It's beautiful in here.
-Yeah.
-It's really nice.
-I like it.
I had an amazing time.
It's just been an experience.
Going on a blind date for the first time
was pretty terrifying,
but, like, thank you for...
thank you for making it so--
Shall we shake each other's hands?
I don't know.
Shake hands.
So...
Are you comfortable talking about, like,
what you're looking for in a relationship?
Sure. I mean...
I don't know.
I mean, I'm looking for a connection.
-Yeah.
-Primarily.
And someone who I can relate to
on a lot of different levels.
-Intellectually, artistically.
-Mm-hmm.
That's what I'm looking for.
That-- And that's--
-I mean, me too. [laughs]
-Yes.
Yeah. [chuckles]
-Huzzah. [laughs]
-Huzzah... [laughs]
[laughs] Um...
I'm...
I guess, like, I'm nervous that, like,
I've only been in this long relationship.
What was, like...
the final straw?
-[exhales]
-Was there a final straw?
Yeah.
We had gone through, like, a long...
low point. And then she...
pitched being in an open relationship.
Interesting.
Which was not necessarily
-something that I felt comfortable with.
-Same.
But she was really excited about it.
So I was like, "Okay."
Um...
And she then started dating someone
almost immediately.
-Oh.
-Uh...
Um...
I did not feel rage.
I did not feel jealousy.
-Indifference?
-She would go over--
Not even that.
Happiness.
And, like, that...
kind of is what set the wheels in motion
of, like, "Maybe...
I'm not actually...
as invested in this relationship
as I kind of thought I was."
Fully get it.
In fact, I feel like
you're super selfless... [inhales]
for even considering just letting her,
essentially, do her thing
when she wanted the open relationship
and you didn't.
And I feel like that says a lot about you
and your character,
that you were open to that to begin with.
Thank-- Thank you.
I'm having a really amazing evening
with you.
And I'm sure you must get this
all the time.
Uh, you just have such an amazing smile
and an amazing laugh
that is just infectious.
It energizes me.
From the moment I first saw you,
like, that was on my mind
and I've just been wanting all evening
to, like, say how wonderful you are.
-I really appreciate that.
-Yeah, yeah.
I know you probably need to get home
to your kids.
I've got to teach class in the morning.
So I should probably-- I feel like
maybe we should wrap things up?
-Um...
-[laughs]
I don't know.
I'm... [stammers] dragging my heels.
-I don't want to leave.
-Yeah?
I'm glad.
[chuckles]
-Yeah? No? Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm, do you...
Uh...
You seem like a...
-a true gentleman.
-Mm-hmm.
And it seems like you...
would want, um...
-to kiss me right now, but...
-[inhales]
it also seems like...
you're looking for permission?
-[chuckles]
-Uh... uh...
You have one hundred percent
identified the situation.
-That is exactly what's happening.
-Um...
-Would you--
-And I'm a lady, so...
-Being that it's the first date--
-Yeah.
-Great. Let's--
-You could...
-On the cheek?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Lovely.
[laughs]
-Thank you.
-I think that's very appropriate.
-I agree.
Great. [chuckling]
-Can I kiss you on your cheek again?
-Okay, sure. [chuckles]
-[table thuds]
-[gasps]
Oh, wait, the table moved.
Okay, the table is telling us
maybe we've done enough kissing.
-Okay.
-[laughs]
-It's a lot of kissing.
-We've overstepped our bounds
on this first date!
[laughs, inhales sharply]
-That was fun.
-Um... it was really fun.
Can I--? Can I walk you out?
Sure. [smacks lips]
-All right.
-Let's go.
Great.
[chuckles] Mmm...
[laughs]
[Shamerick] So funny.
I just want to say, Alex, how...
-beautiful you are and how kind you are.
-Thank you.
There aren't a lot of people like you,
I feel, in the world, Alex.
Thank you so much. That's really sweet.
-I had such an amazing time with you.
-Me too.
Uh...
-Hey, hey! Hey, Jaden.
-Hey.
-Um... uh, Jaden...
-Mm-hmm.
I like you.
I like you too. [chuckles]
-I would really like to see you again.
-Okay.
-Um, I have to be honest though.
I do like you
and I had a wonderful time tonight.
Um... but, for me, I do feel like
it was more of a platonic thing for me.
-Well, shucks. Well, darn.
-[chuckles]
[Ben sighs deeply]
-[driver] I believe we're here.
-Is this you?
-This is me.
-Okay.
Well, uh... it was so wonderful
to get to spend the night.
Mind if I go out this way, instead
of this way, so I don't get hit by a car?
Getting hit. Mm-hmm. [laughs]
-Thank you.
-[Ben] Have a great night.
[exhales sharply]
Um...
-Well... [chuckles]
-Yeah. So, do you...
Maybe we should exchange phone numbers?
-That's a great idea.
-Yeah.
Kat, I'm really...
-digging you. [laughs]
-Good.
-Yeah.
-I'm digging you as well.
Can I--
Do you want to exchange phone numbers?
Okay.
-Sweet.
-Yeah.
-All right.
-Sweet.
All right, Mr. Samuel.
Okay, Ms. Bosworth.
You're in the phone. Officially.
It is official.
-Do you--? Do you know how to do it?
-[laughs]
Look-- Look at you.
-Thank you.
-Have a good night.
-You too.
-Appreciate it.
-Yeah.
-Cool.
-Hey, uh...
can I give you a kiss on the cheek
good night?
-Please.
-Yeah. Great.
-Thank you so much.
-You too.
-It was so nice to meet you.
-Okay.
-Great.
-Bye.
-Great. [chuckles]
-Don't forget your gnocchi.
-I won't. That's right!
-The most important thing.
-The most important... [laughs]
-Thanks, Ben.
-Thank you, Alex.
Seriously, give me a shout.
Absolutely. [chuckles]
[chuckling] Take care.
[vibrant music playing]
♪ Like we're gonna live forever
Ever, ever, ever... ♪
[Ben laughs]
-Nice sweater.
-I was gonna say...
the very same thing to you.
-Yeah. You ready?
-I'm ready!
-Let's do it.
-Have a little picnic.
And you got the wine.
-I got the wine.
-Perfect. Great.
-Great.
-Let's go.
-All right.
-What do you have in there?
I've got a baguette.
And then just a basket full of gnocchi.
[laughing] Oh, no!
♪ Like we're gonna live forever
Ever, ever, ever, hey ♪
♪ You know it's only gonna get better
Better, better, better, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause we're gonna live forever
Ever, ever, ever ♪
[vocalizing]